<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<feed xml:lang="en-US" xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:/posts_feed</id>
  <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page"/>
  <link rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts_feed"/>
  <title>Letters from Trick</title>
  <icon>https://cdn.u.pika.page/j5rLNhX3BaY4brB8x-nMyo4E9XhmithkVZWHC9GZRlM/fn:trick3/plain/s3://pika-production/w8rk7zb6agyqf2ztpltokfqtufdo</icon>
  <updated>2025-08-20T20:48:32Z</updated>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:Post/65974</id>
    <published>2025-08-20T20:48:32Z</published>
    <updated>2025-08-20T20:52:36Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts/a-plushie-of-me"/>
    <title>A plushie? Of me?</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="trix-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="375" width="560" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/OlIYX30KF7Dav_MnToYOBtEF76szIdPvJRG4D0mj35g/s:3840:3840/fn:august2/plain/s3://pika-production/h81m7z4wm8rnpiebctdg746dzsak" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/vehup4SfIAjaZ66NpsPLcKD8z9LfJPnqGArbzl0FPEs/fn:august2/plain/s3://pika-production/h81m7z4wm8rnpiebctdg746dzsak" alt="" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/_TY1DPV7_ZgbYUMWo-2_fJA1no8FsjWzN1QIVvI-ql8/s:1800:1400/fn:august2/plain/s3://pika-production/h81m7z4wm8rnpiebctdg746dzsak"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright, I know what you’re thinking. “Two letters in one month? Something important must be going on!” Hehe… yeah, you’re right!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First of all, there’s &lt;a href="https://plushwonderland.com/collections/lonely-wolf-treat"&gt;another plush campaign&lt;/a&gt; going on right now! It’s not Makeship, but Plush Wonderland!! They were kind enough to reach out and ask to make dolls of me and my friends! Well, we have to reach 50 orders by September 7th, but… it looks like we’re getting close! I think we can do it!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other big news is… &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=f4rhqt2swTw"&gt;Syrup 2 was announced today&lt;/a&gt;! Treat and Mochi will be making a big guest appearance in that one, so I hope you’ll check it out! Maybe I’ll sneak myself in somewhere, too… I’d bring Phoenix, but it takes place before he was born, haha&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Phoenix, he’s taking a nap right now… I’m getting sleepy just looking at him. I think I’ll take a nap, too! I’ll write to you again soon~ *yawn*&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;br&gt;Trick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <summary>Alright, I know what you’re thinking. “Two letters in one month? Something important must be going on!” Hehe… yeah, you’re right! First of all, there’s another plush campaign going on...</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:Post/64799</id>
    <published>2025-08-03T17:01:43Z</published>
    <updated>2025-08-03T17:02:32Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts/happy-birthday-moxie"/>
    <title>Happy Birthday, Moxie!</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="trix-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;
&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="375" width="560" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/50GDX0wCvTql_IIVJUjpMb3cTJQQ_JUhFUxiRLCnJ7w/s:3840:3840/fn:august/plain/s3://pika-production/lneang9c4o8a5d58uzgjqep1pzbb" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/7WTStNZmvcDhLmp3PlYvrzuv9Rm2WZLhPCfzO5z1IJU/fn:august/plain/s3://pika-production/lneang9c4o8a5d58uzgjqep1pzbb" alt="" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/7LB3L5-OFlzFL0Gx6PA527DK52ToJ4Yjc2gZJ0ySZ44/s:1800:1400/fn:august/plain/s3://pika-production/lneang9c4o8a5d58uzgjqep1pzbb"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phoenix and I went to Moxie’s birthday party last Friday! It was such a blast! I let Chai hold Phoenix for a while, and they seemed really happy about that. I love making new friends!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s see, what’s been going on since I last wrote to you…? Oh, &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/3445830/Return_to_Ash/"&gt;Return to Ash&lt;/a&gt; came out! Did you get a chance to play that? &lt;a href="https://badendtheater.com/"&gt;BAD END THEATER&lt;/a&gt; released on consoles, too! Well, I’ve never owned a console, so I don’t know what the difference is… maybe it makes it easier to sit down and play it with your friends? That sounds nice.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of BAD END THEATER, the &lt;a href="https://www.makeship.com/products/maiden-2-0"&gt;maiden&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.makeship.com/products/overlord-2-0"&gt;overlord&lt;/a&gt; plushies are back on sale! Do you remember those? Phoenix was scared of them at first, but now he knows they feel nice to cuddle up against. The campaign is going on for another week, and after that, they’ll be gone forever…! So if you want one, I hope you can get your order in on time!!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Something I heard from Moxie at her birthday party is… over the past week or so, there’s been this big kerfuffle over what games places like itch.io and Steam should be allowed to sell. I guess it’s about adult games…? Moxie seemed really passionate about it, but I don’t know anything about that stuff. She said the comic about her and Treat &lt;a href="https://nomnomnami.com/blog/posts/2025-07-28-moving-my-adult-works-off-itchio"&gt;got de-indexed on &lt;/a&gt;&lt;a href="http://itch.io"&gt;itch.io&lt;/a&gt;… whatever that means. I thought the problem was with games, so it’s weird that it affected comics, too. Anyway, she asked me to &lt;a href="https://stop-paypros.neocities.org/"&gt;pass this link along&lt;/a&gt;—it’s got tons of information on what’s happening, in case you’re someone who buys adult games and comics and wants them to continue to be available to buy online! Sorry that I couldn’t explain it very well… I’ve never bought games or comics like that myself before, but I think it’s important to let people buy them if they want to.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Ooh, one last thing! &lt;a href="https://nomnomnami.com/ask/"&gt;Asks are open&lt;/a&gt; this week, so if you ever wanted to ask Nami something, now’s a good time! Haha, okay, I’ve talked your ear off now so I’ll let you get back to your day… It’s just about lunchtime for Phoenix :) I hope you’re eating well, too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;br&gt;Trick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <summary>Phoenix and I went to Moxie’s birthday party last Friday! It was such a blast! I let Chai hold Phoenix for a while, and they seemed really happy about that....</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:Post/62439</id>
    <published>2025-07-05T16:32:43Z</published>
    <updated>2025-07-05T16:32:44Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts/playing-cards-and-other-news"/>
    <title>Playing cards, and other news!</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="trix-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="375" width="560" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/2to49hd4N4YDfZ7NdGx3YNTyNbMIPoacPn5Vtc14HhA/s:3840:3840/fn:july/plain/s3://pika-production/p1q0y4t9gyaitwccn8ei365mryf1" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/TMj9-mDdGcz-ZdN3i8F9ZklA9fm4lgc6ZXSW-A2-SNc/fn:july/plain/s3://pika-production/p1q0y4t9gyaitwccn8ei365mryf1" alt="" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/ZOwE2L89eEb2AiyReo9EYvR7qQna72fWci6OCqamVi0/s:1800:1400/fn:july/plain/s3://pika-production/p1q0y4t9gyaitwccn8ei365mryf1"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been teaching Phoenix some card games lately! He’s really good at playing go fish. He knows his numbers so well…! I’d say he beats me about half the time, haha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey, have you ever played a game called Balatro? There were some &lt;a href="https://nomnomnami.com/games/treat/downloads/balatreat"&gt;special cards&lt;/a&gt; made for it, including one of me and Phoenix! It looks like you need a computer to play it, so I guess I’ll have to ask someone to let me borrow theirs.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh… that’s right! Here I was talking about card games when there was important news to share this month… &lt;a href="https://store.steampowered.com/app/3445830/Return_to_Ash/"&gt;Return to Ash&lt;/a&gt; will be releasing next Thursday, July 10th! There’s a demo version avaiable right now, so you can play through the beginning of the story, too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Another thing coming on July 10th is…! &lt;a href="https://badendtheater.com/"&gt;BAD END THEATER&lt;/a&gt;, console edition!!! So I guess if you ever wanted to play that game on your Switch, you’ll finally be able to! I heard some of the plushies will be coming back soon too, but… I think that’s still a secret? I don’t mind telling you, though :) I’ll make sure to send you the links before the campaign ends!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One last thing! If you’ve ever worried about missing any big updates, I wanted to direct you to the &lt;a href="https://nomnomnami.com/news/"&gt;news archive&lt;/a&gt;! All the important stuff like release dates and fun stuff for the website is printed there. The issues come out slower than my letters to you, so it’s usually a few months behind… but it’s a good place to check if you just came back from a long vacation and want to know what you missed!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright, Phoenix wants to play more cards, so I gotta end it here. What game should I teach him next? Maybe Crazy Eights…? Haha, I’ll write to you again soon!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;br&gt;Trick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <summary>I’ve been teaching Phoenix some card games lately! He’s really good at playing go fish. He knows his numbers so well…! I’d say he beats me about half the time,...</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:Post/60819</id>
    <published>2025-06-04T16:05:18Z</published>
    <updated>2025-06-04T16:05:19Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts/theres-someone-id-like-you-to-meet"/>
    <title>There’s someone I’d like you to meet</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="trix-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="375" width="560" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/KysvMxhSjir03LZmquYIP53ipAthtMzXuG8bPacxsew/s:3840:3840/fn:june/plain/s3://pika-production/kvv624d61agf1ljpxto86pnhuzfm" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/t-tndL_WKKL5_nWwa-4wK2KVlphb2v4gkMrD9dMMfLA/fn:june/plain/s3://pika-production/kvv624d61agf1ljpxto86pnhuzfm" alt="ash" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/78Nhh54VBWHtKJv32ZsKG4PgcHDXkeMJP8sabXwfOew/s:1800:1400/fn:june/plain/s3://pika-production/kvv624d61agf1ljpxto86pnhuzfm"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I made a new friend! Her name is Ash. We were picking dandelions together, and I stopped to take a picture of her when I remembered I should be sending you a postcard soon… haha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of which… it’s been a while, hasn’t it? There’s a story behind that. It’s a bit of a long one, but… well, I owe you a long letter! You’ll listen, won’t you?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some time after I last wrote to you, Phoenix and I woke up in a very bright place… it was a little scary since the last place I remember falling asleep was in a sunny patch of grass. I didn’t expect it’d get so sunny that it’d blot out the rest of the world! Well, I’m not sure that’s exactly what happened, but it was definitely weird.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phoenix was just as surprised as I was, though. When I woke him up, he said “cheeeeeep!” …which I think means, “Where the heck are we!??!?”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We wandered around that extra-bright place for a little while, until we ran into Ash! She’d just woken up here, too. She pointed to the hospital she came from, but I couldn’t really see it… Oh, and she had this… what was it called? An IV stand! She told us it keeps her from dying. It seems like a pain to walk around tugging one of those along, but she said she was feeling really good since waking up there. I guess she’s normally stuck in bed all day…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, we became friends after that! Since we weren’t sure what else to do, we kept walking around and talking about life and stuff. That’s when we found some dandelions! It was really weird, since the ground seemed too smooth for plants to grow from… but dandelions really do grow everywhere, don’t they?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I tried making Phoenix a small flower crown, but he seemed to want to eat it instead of wear it. After that, Ash and I just kept talking… She seemed like kind of a lonely person, so I was glad to keep her company! It sounded like her world is really different from mine. It was nice getting to hear all about it…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The rest is fuzzy... The next time I woke up, I was finally back in that sunny spot in the grass where I’d fallen asleep before! I kinda wondered if I dreamt the whole thing, but it turned out A LOT of time had passed. At first, I figured the calendar must be wrong, but… I guess I hung out with Ash for a lot longer than I thought!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Anyway, that’s why I haven’t written in a while. Sorry about that! I hope you’ve been doing well. Phoenix says hi, too.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One last thing… I have &lt;a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=Lz5hM24poMI"&gt;a video&lt;/a&gt; to send you! Let’s call it the reward for listening to my long story, haha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I should go now, but I promise I’ll write to you again soon, okay? See ya!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;br&gt;Trick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <summary>I made a new friend! Her name is Ash. We were picking dandelions together, and I stopped to take a picture of her when I remembered I should be sending...</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:Post/57329</id>
    <published>2025-03-31T16:49:40Z</published>
    <updated>2025-03-31T16:49:40Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts/a-picture-from-grannys-book"/>
    <title>A picture from Granny’s book</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="trix-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="375" width="560" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/q08icBwVZg45IvAo9mzVWy22y0wulj7BxhYo1iuqzs0/s:3840:3840/fn:march/plain/s3://pika-production/msyipiquml7bbsyszr7ek33wcy8y" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/0abAdOj1VXpTfF5yIXD5OK6mdmK5YcE_DUdPraTNrM4/fn:march/plain/s3://pika-production/msyipiquml7bbsyszr7ek33wcy8y" alt="" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/Y099fITBaT6IR93jLGZXR1MXiQg5vSH3YOR_eNW5Plw/s:1800:1400/fn:march/plain/s3://pika-production/msyipiquml7bbsyszr7ek33wcy8y"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve been reading the book about caring for birds that Granny gave me, and it has all these funny illustrations! Phoenix is much rounder and cuter than the chicks in here… but I think both are cute, so I wanted to show you.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;April Fools Day is tomorrow! I don’t really like tricking people (despite my name)… so I’m not sure how I’ll celebrate. Maybe I’ll spend it as the one being tricked, haha! The day after that though, there’s going to be daily updates for &lt;a href="https://another-piece-of-candy.thecomicseries.com/"&gt;another piece of candy&lt;/a&gt;. It’s been a while since we’ve had those, hasn’t it? How exciting!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’d heard there was supposed to be a new game announced this month, but it looks like it’ll be coming in April instead. I guess that gives everyone a chance to try out some &lt;a href="https://itch.io/jam/nanoreno-2025"&gt;NaNoRenO&lt;/a&gt; games in the meantime! I wonder what the new game is like…? I wanna be able to tell you about it soon…!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;One last thing I keep forgetting to mention… you can send postcards back to me if you want! Lots of my pen pals have sent drawings of Phoenix and stuff… I love them all, so I put them up on &lt;a href="https://trick.pika.page/guestbook"&gt;this page&lt;/a&gt;!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s all for now. This book I’m reading says baby chicks really love to eat tomatoes, so I’m gonna run to the market to buy one! I hope Phoenix likes it :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;br&gt;Trick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <summary>I’ve been reading the book about caring for birds that Granny gave me, and it has all these funny illustrations! Phoenix is much rounder and cuter than the chicks in...</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:Post/54637</id>
    <published>2025-03-01T06:51:54Z</published>
    <updated>2025-03-01T06:51:55Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts/watching-phoenix-grow-up"/>
    <title>Watching Phoenix grow up</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="trix-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="375" width="560" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/B86lRRoDIhLw99jBKg4EjgTrFFSIpLm_ZkgM5w5u2LM/s:3840:3840/fn:feb/plain/s3://pika-production/qq3mwluuy9t5qcp381n65w6lqxk0" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/KZ4AtLBPC5WxGgqKg-p9H2yU-y27Uysu9DJzUseQP30/fn:feb/plain/s3://pika-production/qq3mwluuy9t5qcp381n65w6lqxk0" alt="" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/RzbFU_h2_wzihoxG-BOGLn3OICPjswPJNCompMXR0sg/s:1800:1400/fn:feb/plain/s3://pika-production/qq3mwluuy9t5qcp381n65w6lqxk0"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey, how’ve you been? I’ve been hanging out in Agaricus waiting for some news to tell you about… Granny and Phoenix have been keeping me real busy, so February flew by before I knew it! I gotta send Mochi a birthday card…!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s see… first of all, there’s a cool new web project called &lt;a href="https://nomnomnami.com/ocsyoucansteal/"&gt;OCs you can steal&lt;/a&gt;! There are all sorts of characters on there, submitted by lots of talented artists. All of the designs are apparently free to use… it makes me want to try writing stories about them! Oh, but I’ve never really written a story before… I’m only good at writing letters! Haha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hmm, what else… there’s &lt;a href="https://nomnomnami.com/blog/posts/2025-02-22-cuter-history-screen"&gt;a new blog post&lt;/a&gt;! It’s a UI tutorial aimed at game developers who use Ren’Py… I’m not really sure what all that means, but I thought I’d let you know in case you were interested!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The BIG news is… a new game is going to be announced soon! I’ve been waiting to see if it’d get announced this month, but I guess there was a slight delay in the schedule… Anyway, it’s a visual novel made in collaboration with a studio. Doesn’t that sound fancy? Haha, I’m excited to see whatever it is!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Alright, Phoenix keeps pecking at my hand to get me to feed him, so… that’s all for now! I’ll write to you again soon!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;br&gt;Trick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <summary>Hey, how’ve you been? I’ve been hanging out in Agaricus waiting for some news to tell you about… Granny and Phoenix have been keeping me real busy, so February flew...</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:Post/21866</id>
    <published>2025-01-12T21:19:42Z</published>
    <updated>2025-01-12T21:19:42Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts/chapter-8-part-2-is-here"/>
    <title>Chapter 8, Part 2 is here!</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="trix-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="416" width="544" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/aQQukTSC0u45NFknOYdHNBWyCrg16XdomE6oYAJe9CE/s:3840:3840/fn:fleabath/plain/s3://pika-production/atlf6q2kx6oy28nesuuwa18exuqb" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/T7710MYUISGnULQXw4mUvH4ARwhR80HgbDcIag3YEI0/fn:fleabath/plain/s3://pika-production/atlf6q2kx6oy28nesuuwa18exuqb" alt="An image with filename: fleabath.png" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/dllpM4KUUzVZx5aghVKK50HMXmamAudWiN2cf8KeLBg/s:1800:1400/fn:fleabath/plain/s3://pika-production/atlf6q2kx6oy28nesuuwa18exuqb"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I have exciting news for you today~!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The next &lt;a href="https://nomnomnami.itch.io/treat-complete"&gt;Lonely Wolf Treat update&lt;/a&gt; just came out! The postcard I’m sending this time is actually an illustration from the new chapter… well, part-chapter? It’s Trick Comes Home, Part 2! The story of when Phoenix and I stayed in Agaricus with… um, I guess you’ll meet her when you play it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I bet you can’t wait to see our story, so I won’t keep you for long! I’ll try to get back on schedule and write to you more often. Oh, and happy new year!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;br&gt;Trick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <summary>I have exciting news for you today~! The next Lonely Wolf Treat update just came out! The postcard I’m sending this time is actually an illustration from the new chapter…...</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:Post/19687</id>
    <published>2024-11-30T22:27:29Z</published>
    <updated>2024-11-30T22:27:30Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts/hanging-in-there"/>
    <title>Hanging in there!</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="trix-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="375" width="560" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/q1FvrrtBJo2Af9XEW6MprQ6ta6GMgCBCYCEg_-PdSyQ/s:3840:3840/fn:november/plain/s3://pika-production/4jl64ytq6rl3493xluqmd1pwzppo" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/ugqHDVvYKm_YmgmhAQgzQu_Q-dQKP0WXp7aep2_2GrM/fn:november/plain/s3://pika-production/4jl64ytq6rl3493xluqmd1pwzppo" alt="An image with filename: november.png" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/BwDI72ap3umzHL4uNgIqXFQohwBLYLILnbXbPdsZVTQ/s:1800:1400/fn:november/plain/s3://pika-production/4jl64ytq6rl3493xluqmd1pwzppo"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hey there, how have you been? Sorry I haven’t written in a while. I’ve been feeling a little down lately…&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The truth is, Phoenix and I ended up attending a funeral recently. I didn’t know the person who passed, but I went along to support a friend. I’d never been to a funeral before… it’s a little tough to keep smiling with such a heavy atmosphere.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Even though something sad had happened, everyone came together and had a lot of nice things to say about the recently departed. They told funny stories, and people cried, but there was a lot of hugging, too… I felt so out of place! Everyone thought Phoenix was cute, though. I think I helped lift their spirits a little.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My master is a lot older than me, and I haven’t seen him in many years now… I realized I don’t actually know for sure whether he’s alive or… not. I’m glad I’m looking for him, but I’m a little scared of what I’ll find at the end of my journey. I hope he’s in good health.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I knew I’d end up writing you a sad letter when I finally got around to it. I think that’s why I avoided it for so long. I hope I didn’t make you worry about me! I’ll be back to my usual self soon, I think.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The holidays are coming up again… and this year I’ll get to celebrate with Phoenix for the first time! I’m really looking forward to that. I hope the rest of 2024 is cozy for you, too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;br&gt;Trick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <summary>Hey there, how have you been? Sorry I haven’t written in a while. I’ve been feeling a little down lately… The truth is, Phoenix and I ended up attending a...</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:Post/8629</id>
    <published>2024-09-29T23:06:03Z</published>
    <updated>2024-09-29T23:06:03Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts/goodbye-cohost"/>
    <title>Goodbye, Cohost!</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="trix-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="375" width="560" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/Ju3B-ESDQnjvwWB3R1u85OuYSyp0L3V8lUsgnIGadeM/s:3840:3840/fn:september/plain/s3://pika-production/rfd7nt6uq5tlj5eg79kw9nuxj28j" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/CblnN6RLGZbaq7AoBoVOUP-MGyMHk2WrubwC4DJzLwA/fn:september/plain/s3://pika-production/rfd7nt6uq5tlj5eg79kw9nuxj28j" alt="An image with filename: september.png" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/XquawIsBcqusAhwqnucHWWD8zOwWCscBKp_DNABaafg/s:1800:1400/fn:september/plain/s3://pika-production/rfd7nt6uq5tlj5eg79kw9nuxj28j"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I saw something really special this month.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s a place called Cohost where these creatures called “eggbugs” live. They’re happy little guys… sometimes they bite, but I think mostly they don’t mean any harm. None of them bit me or Phoenix at least.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Every once in a while, there’s a great migration. I happened to be there to see it… all the eggbugs flew off to find a new home, far away from Cohost.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Have a safe journey, little eggbugs! We wish you well!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Let’s see, what else do I have to share…? There’s a &lt;a href="https://nomnomnami.com/ask/"&gt;new page&lt;/a&gt; where fans will be able to send questions about me and my friends! Make sure to bookmark it so you can read the updates every once in a while.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, and I don’t think I told you about this yet—Treat and her partners opened up &lt;a href="https://nomnomnami.com/comics/moxdonalds/"&gt;a fast food restaurant&lt;/a&gt; in the Netherworld! They didn’t have very many vegetarian options, unfortunately… I heard it shut down pretty quickly too. It made me a little sad to hear that… I wanted to go back at least one more time!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The last thing is, there’s &lt;a href="https://www.makeship.com/products/hero-plush"&gt;another plushie&lt;/a&gt; on the way! But I’ll tell you more about that next month :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It’s time for me to leave Cohost, too. I wonder if I’ll meet any more eggbugs out there? I sure hope so!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;br&gt;Trick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <summary>I saw something really special this month. There’s a place called Cohost where these creatures called “eggbugs” live. They’re happy little guys… sometimes they bite, but I think mostly they...</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:Post/6508</id>
    <published>2024-08-24T03:23:30Z</published>
    <updated>2024-08-24T03:23:31Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts/i-m-in-another-world"/>
    <title>I’m in another world!</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="trix-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="376" width="560" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/ER2lYesKWbiARcmuNWUk1jMW7A5llAeX1FbaZDJTIMc/s:3840:3840/fn:august/plain/s3://pika-production/a4kny8yiwb2v3c51af9a2tvx2zp3" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/Em7n0FKPCfjyyqA52OzxQAU--3ZfPPRS1BX_kJiRh5c/fn:august/plain/s3://pika-production/a4kny8yiwb2v3c51af9a2tvx2zp3" alt="An image with filename: august.png" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/ff1w4tI2mvS0yKvPGHqOUUH6LI7g-v75xPSyoNB67to/s:1800:1400/fn:august/plain/s3://pika-production/a4kny8yiwb2v3c51af9a2tvx2zp3"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;This month, I ended up on a planet called KAIMA! There’s all these scribbly guys eating up the ground… it seems a little dangerous, but I’m okay! Phoenix is more worried than I am, haha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s another Syrup 2 build coming for patrons soon. This will be the third build, after the demo and the one from December 2022! It looks like the game has come a long way, but it’ll still be another year or so before the official release… Lonely Wolf Treat isn’t finished yet either, after all!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of which, Trick Comes Home Part 2 is still planned to be finished this year. I think that means I’m supposed to find Master soon…? I’m really looking forward to that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m glad I could give you some game updates this time! It feels like it’s been a while, haha. I met a girl named SEARINA here, and she asked me if there was any news about KAIMA 2… But I’d only just gotten here! I don’t know anything about a second one. Have you ever heard of KAIMA before…? Tell me what you think of it if you have!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;br&gt;Trick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <summary>This month, I ended up on a planet called KAIMA! There’s all these scribbly guys eating up the ground… it seems a little dangerous, but I’m okay! Phoenix is more...</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:Post/6096</id>
    <published>2024-07-31T19:52:02Z</published>
    <updated>2024-07-31T19:52:03Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts/watching-the-clouds-go-by"/>
    <title>Watching the clouds go by</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="trix-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="375" width="560" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/LI9nGy6Ccaruz8eIUn5Z7nrMqAkKjY_p7DcfQZ0mOWI/s:3840:3840/fn:july/plain/s3://pika-production/an9hp1o68nqmnf8t78v6i0h2q0d4" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/79muzupt8Z5uqrXq_9Dr-VnXGpGLMa5geAeUMMIt7lo/fn:july/plain/s3://pika-production/an9hp1o68nqmnf8t78v6i0h2q0d4" alt="An image with filename: july.png" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/gqrH13Qe3KSGUZCI9rwoSXnMEH3IZGh1iy22X-h-q5E/s:1800:1400/fn:july/plain/s3://pika-production/an9hp1o68nqmnf8t78v6i0h2q0d4"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Isn’t it so funny how much the sky changes in a day? But it’s always the same, too… the same sun, the same moon, the same stars. It all looks different depending on what time you’re looking at it… That’s what I’ve been thinking about lately. Maybe I’m just looking at the sky too much? Haha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’ve gone lots of places, but I started feeling… what is it? Homesick? But I visited Treat for her birthday a few months ago. It’s too soon to feel homesick, I think. Am I just sad because I haven’t found Master yet? I’m not sure. Phoenix doesn’t have any insights either… just chirps :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I don’t have any exciting news for you this month. Still just working on finding my way “home”! I hope you’re feeling comfortable wherever you are. And if it’s hot, I hope you’re staying cool! I’ll always think you’re cool anyway.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thanks for reading my letters. Phoenix says thanks, too! Or, more accurately… “cheep”!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;br&gt;Trick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <summary>Isn’t it so funny how much the sky changes in a day? But it’s always the same, too… the same sun, the same moon, the same stars. It all looks...</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:Post/5123</id>
    <published>2024-06-30T04:30:00Z</published>
    <updated>2024-06-30T04:22:35Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts/greetings-from-tokyo"/>
    <title>Greetings from Tokyo!</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="trix-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="600" width="800" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/WaZbNGSIylU7OfvBW8EzMotw7mKbqZ0B9xPdBVodBG8/s:3840:3840/fn:tokyo/plain/s3://pika-production/rbgyrh0yr59y801ld6n9faswp0qn" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/qEeeHK_0RJauyUWA3NGZOhalg3wfmIK36aXC2tL-eUU/fn:tokyo/plain/s3://pika-production/rbgyrh0yr59y801ld6n9faswp0qn" alt="An image with filename: tokyo.png" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/cqpqiIKj6eXaDYy2vMtkQRasdY1kx0OaAKj6CQEUkuk/s:1800:1400/fn:tokyo/plain/s3://pika-production/rbgyrh0yr59y801ld6n9faswp0qn"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phoenix and I are still running around the human world this month. This time I’m sending a picture of when we went to Ueno Toshogu Shrine! It was shiny, so Phoenix liked it a lot. I prayed to find Master soon, like always.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We also visited Chinzanso Garden. It was beautiful! Unfortunately, it was dark when we were walking around, so I couldn’t get a good picture… But there was one thing I was excited to find:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="599" width="801" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/tO74kEocQiVkVkPdoHCW-5YqcoArjm1sK1psZtqjYVI/s:3840:3840/fn:garden/plain/s3://pika-production/tajmddkrxbop6beq9hb7eesli5vb" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/y3CdDdJpd2AYUGS3woRYa-0nX1FsDR4mArc2kq7i7Yk/fn:garden/plain/s3://pika-production/tajmddkrxbop6beq9hb7eesli5vb" alt="An image with filename: garden.png" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/Vo3xDUJGazE5JPBcFULhiES7bIGUd5HA7-KeoQ108nA/s:1800:1400/fn:garden/plain/s3://pika-production/tajmddkrxbop6beq9hb7eesli5vb"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There was a statue of a chicken god! The sign says “Chickens have long been recognized as guardians of peace and happiness since they give up flight to leisurely stroll around gardens.” Did you know that in Japanese, the word for chicken sounds like “garden bird”? Heheh, I’m seeing Phoenix in a new way :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Sorry I couldn’t get a good picture of the statue… I just thought it was nice that humans had this much admiration for chickens. I love them, too! Thanks for being a guardian of peace and happiness, Phoenix!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m leaving Japan in a couple days, so I’ll tell you about some brand new adventures next month. See you then :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;br&gt;Trick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <summary>Phoenix and I are still running around the human world this month. This time I’m sending a picture of when we went to Ueno Toshogu Shrine! It was shiny, so...</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:Post/4056</id>
    <published>2024-05-30T14:40:31Z</published>
    <updated>2024-05-30T14:42:46Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts/greetings-from-osaka"/>
    <title>Greetings from Osaka!</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="trix-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="653" width="874" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/ful0q6dyY_j5Zsh1n0ni8hy2-MSitoGf43SB5ikge6g/s:3840:3840/fn:osaka/plain/s3://pika-production/hgoc6ramdh2qwi46ak8explf8zod" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/vGFaaX8SHANcJ5gj-Zcc6jFWkWnoiBMQUd-jU55qHiE/fn:osaka/plain/s3://pika-production/hgoc6ramdh2qwi46ak8explf8zod" alt="An image with filename: osaka.png" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/E5_MP3BJ9he4xPKaNzBcihkbHSoue-sHm1WjqWI2KAo/s:1800:1400/fn:osaka/plain/s3://pika-production/hgoc6ramdh2qwi46ak8explf8zod"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Phoenix and I have been traveling somewhere special… it’s a place with lots and lots of humans—you might even be able to go there, too! But in case you can’t, I took some photos :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The first one is in Dotonbori, near Shinsaibashi. It gets really crowded on the weekends! There was so much going on, I had a hard time absorbing it all… so I’m glad I stopped to take a picture to remember the day by.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After that, we went to Ikeda! Wanna know why? It’s because… there’s a Cup Noodles Museum!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--jpg"&gt;



    &lt;img height="767" width="998" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/BTMrpnYxY9dVax3IWGzx9rRqeiWyd9_URS-BBvls_NQ/s:3840:3840/fn:noodles/plain/s3://pika-production/6f8ypycmj4l5dyhstadp7bjrtl82" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/0OArAvLLrtG1mBKvGftsKgIu_zYwoP3T4Xn3JarNAl4/fn:noodles/plain/s3://pika-production/6f8ypycmj4l5dyhstadp7bjrtl82" alt="An image with filename: noodles.jpg" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/arZT1EQ4v2wVbXijr5uHm_pWGJS0EntRrUX20i8S_i4/s:1800:1400/fn:noodles/plain/s3://pika-production/6f8ypycmj4l5dyhstadp7bjrtl82"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treat told me about how she ate lots of cup noodles when she first moved to Frosting… so when I found out there was a museum for it, I had to go.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;They let you create your own, too! I drew Phoenix on mine :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--jpg"&gt;



    &lt;img height="918" width="675" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/Ampb6CMKauJeGacFymmaWOBdW2BzFf7UUPGStX3ZBbg/s:3840:3840/fn:phoenix/plain/s3://pika-production/bzvzyxk29jjx7kh6jqdfj3445beq" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/o6ltmmwCOvA_CgnqRJ4LCJE5T3ov_fh6evPh112iAfo/fn:phoenix/plain/s3://pika-production/bzvzyxk29jjx7kh6jqdfj3445beq" alt="An image with filename: phoenix.jpg" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/bJnUSg63i4m44iwZMN2thHGPEuGdncJ8kCV2CF__AsU/s:1800:1400/fn:phoenix/plain/s3://pika-production/bzvzyxk29jjx7kh6jqdfj3445beq"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Pretty good, right? For the flavor, I had to pick… curry!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I won’t have any actual news for a while, so I hope you don’t mind me sharing some of my human world adventures like this. Next month I’ll be in Tokyo! I’ll write again soon :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;br&gt;Trick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <summary>Phoenix and I have been traveling somewhere special… it’s a place with lots and lots of humans—you might even be able to go there, too! But in case you can’t,...</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:Post/3230</id>
    <published>2024-04-30T21:41:25Z</published>
    <updated>2024-04-30T21:41:25Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts/happy-birthday-treat"/>
    <title>Happy Birthday, Treat!</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="trix-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="375" width="560" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/oC9SmNgT9XYSTdsdIJZonBy9VrPIZfOxEcsHKawURHU/s:3840:3840/fn:april/plain/s3://pika-production/oviov2izwvhmsdw42nbfia6pv7tw" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/ZImpQyVOfMLe5k4lqRicyH0tUn5IC8NzDVzvDxWqs20/fn:april/plain/s3://pika-production/oviov2izwvhmsdw42nbfia6pv7tw" alt="An image with filename: april.png" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/4lHvdrXpi-aGPP23ZHk5gkksoaZ6XSr0iRKgF-FopCI/s:1800:1400/fn:april/plain/s3://pika-production/oviov2izwvhmsdw42nbfia6pv7tw"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;April 30th is Treat’s birthday! I bought a ticket back to Mount Sorbet so I could make it to her birthday party. Mochi baked a cake! It has strawberries in it… yum!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I actually have some great news to share, too! A new &lt;a href="https://nomnomnami.itch.io/treat-complete"&gt;Lonely Wolf Treat&lt;/a&gt; update is out—don’t get TOO excited, because it doesn’t have more of Chapter 8 yet… but I heard there’s some really good bonus content hidden in there. Check the &lt;a href="https://nomnomnami.itch.io/treat-complete/devlog/723557/v085-patch-notes"&gt;patch notes&lt;/a&gt; for details!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m really glad that I met Treat. Lately I’ve been thinking… who knows what would’ve happened if I joined a different pack instead? Treat and her family have been so nice to me… I hope I can repay their kindness somehow!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;That’s all I have to say today. Sorry that you couldn’t come to Treat’s party… I hope you can do something nice to celebrate it wherever you are!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;br&gt;Trick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <summary>April 30th is Treat’s birthday! I bought a ticket back to Mount Sorbet so I could make it to her birthday party. Mochi baked a cake! It has strawberries in...</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:Post/2298</id>
    <published>2024-03-26T20:00:00Z</published>
    <updated>2024-03-26T19:51:44Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts/i-m-surfing-the-net"/>
    <title>I'm surfing the net!</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="trix-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="375" width="560" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/cuFjFuvdxrTvCHhlhoPXXVZhLRLmUDuMyOZroDB1Npc/s:3840:3840/fn:march/plain/s3://pika-production/opfh13sz16lwoj1rw1zvp6n8le7p" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/2bOvD_M6_Qy_pcbCy4Eh2SHDYAv76nYfPYOY06n2-W8/fn:march/plain/s3://pika-production/opfh13sz16lwoj1rw1zvp6n8le7p" alt="An image with caption: (art by chunderfins)" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/oUABfs7xM3NX1G6pHTy0aX_A6aAA4mR0_Hsn5utrEqk/s:1800:1400/fn:march/plain/s3://pika-production/opfh13sz16lwoj1rw1zvp6n8le7p"&gt;

    &lt;figcaption class="attachment__caption"&gt;
      (art by chunderfins)
    &lt;/figcaption&gt;
&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Witches make some incredible things! The librarian here told me that this box is full of charms that read “1” or “0”… I don’t get it, but there’s a fun place called &lt;a href="https://neocities.org/"&gt;Neocities&lt;/a&gt; I’ve been exploring. People build their own pages and put whatever they want on it, so I’m having fun learning all sorts of things! &lt;a href="https://nomnomnami.neocities.org/"&gt;Here’s a site&lt;/a&gt; that might interest you too :)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The plush campaign for maiden and overlord ended last week. They sold over 800 each…! I didn’t expect it’d be so many!! Did you get yours? Or are you holding out for the hero? I heard he’s coming later this year… then the set will be complete! I wonder if there’ll be Treat plushies someday? I’d love to see that.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I’m having trouble remembering what else I wanted to tell you this month… I think I’ve been spending too much time on the computer. Phoenix started pecking at my hand after a few hours… he gets really impatient sometimes, but he’s probably just bored because he can’t read! Sorry, Phoenix… I’ll buy you some really tasty seeds to make up for it.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember to get up and play outside sometimes, too!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;br&gt;Trick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <summary>Witches make some incredible things! The librarian here told me that this box is full of charms that read “1” or “0”… I don’t get it, but there’s a fun...</summary>
  </entry>
  <entry>
    <id>tag:trick.pika.page,2005:Post/1315</id>
    <published>2024-02-29T21:26:32Z</published>
    <updated>2024-02-29T21:26:32Z</updated>
    <link rel="alternate" type="text/html" href="https://trick.pika.page/posts/happy-leap-day"/>
    <title>Happy Leap Day!</title>
    <content type="html">&lt;div class="trix-content"&gt;
  &lt;div class="attachment-gallery"&gt;&lt;figure class="attachment attachment--preview attachment--png"&gt;



    &lt;img height="375" width="560" data-zoom-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/RpolBsSgcp_eQMhWMOXLAHYtmBUNTq2Miy-yp6ETc-4/s:3840:3840/fn:february/plain/s3://pika-production/y2yow169eqk438sdqd749wabxf5p" data-original-src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/pda9PE7zF4z90yjsFycmX9ruRni8aymfxC8OeRM_ZUQ/fn:february/plain/s3://pika-production/y2yow169eqk438sdqd749wabxf5p" alt="An image with filename: february.png" src="https://cdn.u.pika.page/XRjfJ6T5jtKQP69fTCWPUACgORZRkACTUlxjbk6VYC8/s:1800:1400/fn:february/plain/s3://pika-production/y2yow169eqk438sdqd749wabxf5p"&gt;

&lt;/figure&gt;&lt;/div&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Today’s the day that only comes once every 4 years! I wanted to save my letter for this special occasion… Hehe, I hope you didn’t think I forgot to send it!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Remember last year when I told you about the underling plushies? They’re making &lt;a href="https://www.makeship.com/products/maiden"&gt;maidens&lt;/a&gt; and &lt;a href="https://www.makeship.com/products/overlord"&gt;overlords&lt;/a&gt; now too! There’s about a week left in the campaign, so I hope you’re able to snag one if you want! Phoenix is a little scared of them since they’re so much bigger than him, haha.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Oh, I think you’ll be happy to hear this, too! The &lt;a href="https://lonely-wolf-treat.carrd.co/"&gt;Lonely Wolf Treat website&lt;/a&gt; got a makeover this month!! That was a few weeks ago now, so maybe you already noticed… but the cast page is loaded with character profiles! (A little weird to call my friends “characters”… hey, Phoenix isn’t in here! That’s not fair…!)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Speaking of Treat, progress on the rest of Chapter 8 is coming along smoothly. There’s gonna be a patron build available in May, and public release is planned for later this year. I’ll finally get to see Master again… I wonder if he and Phoenix will get along?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;There’s some other news I can think of, but it’s pretty far off… so I’ll save it for next time! I hope you leap around a lot today! (That’s what you’re supposed to do on Leap Day, right…?)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Your friend,&lt;br&gt;Trick&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</content>
    <summary>Today’s the day that only comes once every 4 years! I wanted to save my letter for this special occasion… Hehe, I hope you didn’t think I forgot to send...</summary>
  </entry>
</feed>
